Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jason-llanes (LinkedIn) www.facebook.com/jsnllanes19/ (Personal)

Top Skills
Technical Support
Data Entry
Git

Jason Llanes

Flutter Developer | Mobile Application Developer | Web Developer | Quality Assurance

Cagayan De Oro City, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Summary

As a Mobile Application Developer, I create and maintain Android applications for various clients. I have a bachelor's degree in information technology from STI College, where I learned the fundamentals of programming, web development, and database management. I have more than two years of work experience in the field of mobile application development, using Java and other technologies to build user-friendly and functional apps. I also have teaching experience, as I was a course instructor at MyCode, where I taught children how to create simple games using Scratch. I enjoy applying my skills and knowledge to solve problems, create value, and empower users. I am passionate about learning new technologies, sharing my expertise, and collaborating with others. I am always looking for opportunities to improve my skills, expand my network, and contribute to the growth and innovation of the industry.

Experience

Department of Information and Communications Technology - Philippines
Information System Analyst II
September 2024 - Present (4 months)

Misamis Oriental Provincial Office, T. Chavez Street, Cagayan de Oro City

CyTech International

1 year 1 month

Web Developer March 2024 - Present (10 months)

Cagayan De Oro City, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Quality Assurance Specialist
December 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Philippines

CLENRO

Mobile Application Developer

July 2021 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Cagayan De Oro City, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

MyCode

Course Instructor

July 2021 - January 2022 (7 months)

I teach children's and kids, a simple game development using Scratch.

Innovuze Solutions, Inc.

Creatives

January 2019 - March 2019 (3 months)

Cagayan De Oro City, Northern Mindanao, Philippines

Education

STI College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (June 2024)

STI College

High School Diploma, ICT · (2018 - 2020)

STI College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (August 2018)